

Portugal

+351 926 843 295

@ franciscoandre.farp@gmail.com

My Portfolio in ffarps.github.io

in My linkedin

OBJECTIVE

My name is Francisco André Rodrigues Pereira, I'm 22 years old, from Mirandela, and I graduated from the Polytechnic Institute of Bragança with a degree in Informatics Engineering.

During the third year of the course and after completing it, I was awarded two research grants by the Centre for Research in Digitalisation and Intelligent Robotics (CeDRI).

Proactive and dedicated, ready to achieve great things.

EXPERIENCE

Out 2023-now Personal Projects Development

Developing personal projects related to areas, frameworks and tools in which I want to invest some time and upgrading my technical know-how, my current goal is to apply the theoretical knowledge which I learned during my degree in these projects.

My web Portfolio in https://ffarps.github.io

Jul 2023-Sep 2023 Research Fellowship at CeDRI

CeDRI, Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Contributed to an OpenZDM project related to developing a C# and OpenGl-based tool in Unity 3D, that aims to reduce defects in production chains in a car factory in the assembly and body

shop zones.

Jul 2022-Jan 2023 Research Fellowship at CeDRI

CeDRI, Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Worked on developing Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) apps in Unity, using different frameworks and tools, such as MRTK, ARCore, Vuforia SDK and ARFoundation.

EDUCATION

Oct 2019-Jul 2023 Degree in Informatics Engineering

Instituto Politécnico de Bragança

Scientific Areas: Computer Science, Computer Engineering, Mathematics, Information Systems. Worked on many projects related to Web Development, Computer Architecture, Networking, 3D Modeling, Machine Learning, Data Structures, SQL and IoT.

High School Diploma

Agrupamento de Escolas de Mirandela

Science and technology

LANGUAGES

2016-2019

HARD SKILLS

HARD SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS

Portuguese - native English - proficient **Programming**: C#, TypeScript, Python, Java, JavaScript, Rust, etc

Source Control: Git Linux and Bash

Unity 3D

Databases: SQL and NoSQL

Self-taught Attention to detail Technical Writing Teamwork